Youtube subtitles download by mo.dbxdb.com
so we're joking around here
with uh who are you
[Laughter]
anders heilsper chief randomizer on the
c-sharp team
[Laughter]
cool and what are we yeah what are we
doing here what are we doing here
so and we're also here with dan
fernandez oh yeah product manager
program manager product manager on the
c-sharp team
yeah and last time we talked to anders
uh let's last couple times we talked
about
the need for to make it easier for those
of us writing
in say c sharp to interact with sql
and you had mentioned something briefly
about well we're thinking about that for
c
sharp 3.0 blah blah blah now we have
project link
what's going on well so we thought about
it
yeah i mean so we talked about that the
big disconnect between
uh databases and general purpose
programming languages and that's
effectively what we've
worked on for the last 18 probably 18 24
months
um and now at the pdc
we are showing wow the first preview of
the link project
link stands for it's linq for language
integrated query
and it's effectively sort of in a
nutshell it is
taking query set operations and
transforms and making them first class
concepts
in the dot net framework and that means
you know in the in the
clr itself it means in programming
languages in apis and so forth
such that you get a completely unified
query experience across
objects and xml and data all the various
or
forms that that data occurs in in your
applications
so now uh what is this what does it look
like i mean
i'm thinking of you know say select star
from some table where what does that
look like in c sharp well we'll take a
look at in a little bit here i'll show
you
what the code looks looks like let me
first talk a little bit about how how
it sort of differs from from traditional
uh uh
approaches to this i mean and indeed you
know like select star from or whatever
yes you may have written that and and if
you think back
maybe it wasn't so long you wrote it but
but you probably wrote it in quotes
you know and you you gave it as an
argument to new secret command
of select star blah blah blah with
placeholders for the arguments etc etc
and of course when you wrote it there
was no compile time type checking nor
was there any intellisense or or
anything because effectively
you have sort of the language you're
writing in c sharp and then you have the
language in quotes
sequel which is not at all understood in
in in that context and
that sort of just sort of scratches the
surface to illustrate the deep
mismatches that we have between that
data domain and the
object domain um it's not just
that the integration story is kind of
funny in that you have a language within
the other language but also at a deeper
level like
things like objects versus relational
algebra
novel types versus not different
standard functions different data types
you know everything is different between
these two domains and we can do so much
better by integrating the world so that
when you write your queries in c
sharp it's like a natural part of the c
sharp language you know what i mean when
you write your
your predicates like where you want to
say where blah blah blah well it's a c
sharp
expression of type bool that you're
you're writing there in terms of
you know the stuff that you're querying
and so forth and you get
intellisense you get compile time type
checking and you get to write the
queries
not just against your database but also
against an in-memory array of customers
that you have
using exactly the same syntax or against
an xml document
so that's sort of where we're going with
this stuff fantastic
now clearly have you been working with
the sql team because they've done some
interesting work in 2005 with
being able to write story procedures in
c sharp
um and work like that so i'm sure you
guys have worked together at all or well
we we talk all the time obviously
and and and the sql clr uh support in
yukon
is sort of laying the foundation for
hosting manage code inside sql server
the stuff we're showing here is sort of
like what could you do with that in the
future and then so far
we're outside the server itself so it so
this stuff that i'm going to demo you
here and
the bits we're hanging out with the pdc
all run on the mid tier
not inside the server but going forward
that is absolutely a direction that
we're looking at
fantastic so um shall we look at some
code
sure i mean we can always talk more too
no no no no no
let's let's always let's look at some
code here
so what i have here is just um a little
program that has some sample data and
this
in this particular case here um it's
just an array of customers that i've
gotten from somewhere it doesn't
actually matter where they came from i
could have just knew them up right now
and customers have you know names and
addresses and an embedded collection of
orders and so forth so now i'm going to
try and write some queries against this
stuff
um my first little query is just going
to say give me all the customers and
then i'm going to call my object dumper
which is a little
little piece of code written using
reflection that just dumps
uh the contents of of my customers so if
i try and run this
here you'll just see a list of all the
customers and you'll see this is
actually all the northwind customers
that i've just put into objects and it
has
you know they each have a bunch of
properties um
the first thing you note here is
var q equals customers var is local
variable type inference so this is a
basically the ability to declare local
variables and have their type be
inferred from
the value that you assigned to them so
this is exactly the same as saying
customer array queue
equals customer because customers is of
type customer array
um anyway let me let me let me first try
and query here and the first thing i'm
going to do is maybe filter this down to
fewer customers maybe those that are in
the city of london so i can say
dot where and then c
calling the customer c c dot city
london and let's try and run this
and now you see my list of customers is
down to fewer um indeed if we scroll
sidewards here
we can sort of see that they're all in
the city of london
um now i could apply another operator
let me actually put this on
separate lines here and then apply a
select operator again calling the
customer c give me
c dot company name now let's try and run
this
and now we just see the company names of
the customers
in london um so
if you've done some c shop coding you're
going to wonder what what what the hell
is this stuff where where what
what is it he's writing here um so first
of all
um the argument to where and the
argument to select
are our sample functions or lambda
expressions we call them and they're
effectively an an evolution of
anonymous methods that are present in c
sharp two o okay
um in this case here though we have even
more type inference than we used to so
what i'm really writing here is a little
function that takes a customer c is an
argument and returns
c dot city equals london which is a type
bool which the where operator wants to
see
absolutely um now but you'll note that
we can infer what the type of c
is so you don't have to say customer ceo
but delegate a customer say you open
curly return blah blah blah blah
you just write it you know right in
there in situ and we infer
all of the all of the the types that
surround it same is true for the for the
select guy here
now the second thing you're going to
wonder is like where did this wear come
from and this select guy you know
because an array doesn't have a wear or
a selection
and a new feature we have in c sharp 3 0
is what we call
extension methods which is the ability
to extend
an existing type with new methods and
this sort of sounds like magic but it's
actually just based on some simple
lookup rules for
static methods okay and the way it works
here is that because i'm
importing the namespace system.query and
because system.query
defines a bunch of extension methods
okay like where and select
that all work on anything that implement
i innumerable of t
then because arrays implement
innumerable of t for some t
um i get where's and selects that i in
fact get a whole
library of methods like order by group
by any all
et cetera et cetera you know and and
these methods all composed to form a
complete query language that i can apply
to any dot net array or collection
fantastic so generics actually uh the
foundation for deep enabler in this yes
because generics make the type system
rich enough now that we can express all
the flow of type information that has to
occur
in a query very cool now even so you
might go gosh this is looking a little
geeky you know with these arrows and
stuff and whatever and so
on top of these on top of these
query methods we have a thing that we
call query expressions
um and that's effectively the ability to
write these queries
using a more query like syntax you asked
earlier does it look like sql what does
it look like well let me show you
what it what it looks like i could write
this very same query as
like this var q equals from
c in customers where c dot city
equals equals london
select c dot company and it would mean
precisely the same
now the way this works
and my analogy here is think of the for
each statement and i'm sure you've used
a gazillion topics right
yep now for each is actually a pattern
over first calling get a numerator and
then emitting a while statement that
calls move next on the enumerator and
obtains the current property and so
forth and you don't actually
think about that day to day you just use
for each exactly
the same is true here this is the same
but for queries
okay when you write from where select
we turn it into calls to the where
method and the select method on the
collection that you're querying
underneath but you don't have to think
about that that's
just an implementation detail and the
method could be implemented by the
collection itself or it could be an
extension method as is the case here
and it could actually come from
somewhere else and that's how we get
query syntax for
any arbitrary collection now does that
does it have to follow that pattern
because
logically after be doing so much sql
i i want to say select first then from
then where yes
so does it matter or it does matter it
doesn't matter from comes before select
okay um unlike sql now there you go why
is that
well um think of a couple of things
first of all
what if i were to write select
select and now i want statement
completion uh
what am i going to show you here okay
every variable in the universe we don't
know where it's coming from yet
so so there's a bit of a problem with
the flow of things in sql you need to
know the from class before you can give
help on the select clause
okay and logically sql is funny in that
the scope of the variable flows
backwards
you introduce it in the from clause but
it is in scope above the from clause
true so so things don't come in a
natural order in sql
and we've reordered such that things
flow
scope flows down like it always does in
your program
and things happen in the order you save
them first you take things from
somewhere then you filter them and then
you select stuff out of them
now if you look at x query you'll note
that they actually have the same
ordering of the operators as well so
it's not like
like we're treading completely uncharted
ground
here there's there's precedent for this
um and there are some
some more reasons for why it's important
to have the select at the end
when it gets into hierarchical queries
and so forth where the select cost can
get
very very large and you really want to
see what's in scope before you write
this large body of
of code in the select anyway um just to
sort of show you
let me delete the first version of the
query here and then try and run
and you'll see boom we get the same
result and in fact if you were to look
at the il it's precisely the same code
now the next thing you're going to want
to
look at here is projections
so in sql you can select x comma y comma
c from
some table or whatever and you can you
can effectively create structural types
on the fly
you know just by selecting a variety of
columns out of out of your table
now in the object world there is no
notion of structural types at least not
in a dot net type system um
okay and what we would do here instead
is we would convert objects from one
type to another
in order to project that would be the
analogy so if i have a bunch of
customers here and let's say i want to
create a phone list out of it
well i would i would effectively project
into maybe a new contact class that i've
written
so i might say select new contact
of c dot company name comma c dot phone
if you see what i'm saying and that
would be my projection i would
change my array of customers into a
sequence of contacts and i picked out
company name and phone of course now i
would have to go write this contact
class absolutely and introduce
constructors and properties and so forth
and that's a bit of a
pain you know if you had to write a new
class for every
select statement that you wrote now
to alleviate that what we support is now
this thing we call anonymous type so i
can simply say new
open curly i can close curly here
and what i'm doing here is i am saying
give me an instance
of something that has two fields or two
properties company name and phone
and then just project them out from the
customers and then give me back a
sequence of that
now now this thing i'm creating here is
just like any clr
class it's just that it's created by the
compiler instead of having being created
by me
and it is its shape is inferred from how
i used it in the query
and then the query gives me a sequence
of those back and
here we see local variable type
inference comes to the rescue since i
can't say the name of this type
local variable type inference allows
allows me to not say it
and still be strongly typed okay now
let's first try and run it and you'll
see the
the shape of this is yes i now have a
sequence of something that has company
name and phone
two fields and it's strongly typed
because i found these field names
through reflection
indeed in here i could have written for
each
x var x in
q
console.write line of x dot company name
for example
and once the ide gets uh aware enough of
these
extensions there would actually be
statement completion right here so when
i said x dot it would show me company
name and phone those are the two fields
that are available
and if i run here you'll see that i just
get the company names if i introduce an
error you'll see that i actually get an
error message the compiler has type
checked this stuff so
this isn't late bound script-like stuff
even though i never said it i never said
a type anywhere
the type has flowed out of my query and
into my for each and the compiler knows
what's what's going on
so this is sort of like the difference
between doing it the easy way with with
no typing
or doing it the hard way where the type
is there but you don't have to say it
all the time
very nice okay let me just show you a
few more things
one of the things that's interesting of
course in the object world is that we
have
uh hierarchical data um
and i could in here for example well
actually let me start
in one way um and say from seeing
customers and then also from onc.orders
because all
customers have an orders collection so
let me
effectively join customers with their
own orders
um and then from that select out the
company name
o.order date and o dot total
and let's try and run this and you'll
see now a sort of
sql like shape or result where i have
repetition in the outer column
okay because i'm seeing the orders of
the customers in london
um and of course the company name
repeats many times
um now i could actually introduce
another predicate here and say oh dot
order date
dot year equals 1997.
run this and now we only get those
orders that are in 1997.
um now this is a very sequel like shape
or result sort of rectangular do you
know what i mean just rows and columns
but one of the things that's key about
objects is that we have
hierarchy hierarchical shapes of data
it's very very common when you code with
objects you don't have nested
collections and so forth
and we support that ability in in our
query language here as well so i could
change this query to say from each
customer select and project
out company name
and then project out orders equals and
then let's take this guy
and make it a sub query that's nested
um like whoops
statement completion is still sort of
fighting me a little bit on the
indentation here
but we'll put it where it's supposed to
go like so okay now let's try and run
this
and now you'll see well actually now
you'll see first that at the outer level
we have company names and orders
now my object number is not drilling
into the nested collection right now but
i can tell it to go in
one level deeper here by adding comma
one
and then run and now you'll see that i
actually get a hierarchically shaped
result set where i get company name and
orders at the outer level and then
inside the orders collection i have
order dates and totals
for each customer and of course i can
also apply
ordering to this so i could say take
these guys and order by
old dot total descending
in here and now you'll see
the result has all of the orders for
each customer ordered by descending
total so i always see the top
the the largest customer first now is
there a limit to the number of
of uh arrays so you know the dimensions
well it's it works for a single
dimensional array so any it works for
anything that implements innumerable of
t and multi-dimensional arrays don't
implement inew or volte
but it works for a list of customers or
any collection that implements
innumerability which which
almost all of our collections do so it's
not just limited to arrays obviously
sure just to show you also um
a few other things with with this stuff
maybe i should show you how it works
with
uh relational data yes uh because i'm
sure people
will will be very interested in that so
let me try and switch to another project
here
and talk a little bit about uh
this api that we have called d clarity
oh sorry d
link which is uh the next version
of the future version of ado.net that
supports strongly typed
language integrated data access
[Music]
effectively you can use this in in one
of two ways you can write a bunch of
classes like customers and orders you
can write them yourself and then you can
put attributes on the classes that say
this class corresponds to this table in
my database
and on the properties you can put
attributes that say this property
corresponds to this column in the
database
and then we can persist those things for
you in a database
but more typically is is probably that
you would point at an existing database
and say please give me
an object-oriented view of this database
yes um
and that's what i've done here with the
with the same northwind database um
and and effectively what comes out of
that then if we look at the code here
um is a strongly typed view of my
database where i get a class called
northwind
that contains all of the tables of the
database okay
typed as table of blah where blah then
is order or customer or whatever and
then if we scroll down a little bit
you'll see down here
[Music]
here is a class customer that has a
bunch of storage for
the fields of a customer object uh or
the
effectively corresponding to the columns
in the database and a bunch of
properties allow me to access
and we also have the relations map so
customers has a nested orders relation
that actually maps to
join and with the orders table in the
database beautiful and so forth
so using this stuff now i can
i can actually write and access this
database and write language integrated
queries
okay but i'm just going to start out by
newing up a north wind
as you see here then i'm going to attach
a log
to my north wind connection and you
should think of this as a strongly type
connection to my database
this effectively gives me a strongly
typed view
of the data that's in there now i can
just say
db dot and then i get oops db dot i get
statement completion you see
here we have you know customers uh right
here
i can simply just say give me the whole
customers table and then let's run the
object number again
uh to see what what happens there and
then the first thing you see in the dump
is that we spit out because we attach
the log we spit out the query that we
sent to the database which consisted of
select address city company name blah
blah blah from customers
and then here we see all of the
customers coming back and effectively
what we do is
we fire off the query and then we take
the incoming result set and we knew up
objects from the result set as they come
in
now let me now try and write exactly the
same query but this
time against relational data so whoops
so i'm going to write froms
from c in db.customers where c dot city
equals london select
c dot company name
so just what we had before absolutely
and let's try and run this and here you
see
first the query that goes across is
select company name from customers where
city equals blah
and then back comes exactly the same
city and this
effectively shows you how using
precisely the same
query syntax i can
uh query either in memory data
in an array or a database um
and that's sort of really the power of
language integrated query is that it
gives you unification
across the different domains of data
now we do a bunch more stuff in the
d-link api
we can do we can do change tracking to
the entities that you fetch from the
database
we can push the changes back by
generating dynamic sql or calling stored
procedures to do the updates
and so forth there's a whole bunch of
depth be behind that too and that's all
included also in the preview bits that
that we've uh
that we're giving out at the pdc okay
final thing i'm gonna show is how does
this work with with xml
there's a lot of stuff here um let's go
back to
a little demo project here and then just
try and write
a little bit of xml code here
i'm just going to new up an xml element
using the
uh the x-link
xlinq api that we have that gives us
language integrated query
for xml and effectively this
think of this api as doing two new
things for xml
first it gives you language integrated
query capabilities
which are as powerful really as xpath
and
query it's like having the power of x
query
inside c sharp or vb um the other thing
we do
with the with the xlink api is that we
we take all of the lessons we've learned
from the w3c dom
over the last 10 years of usage and we
and we fixed them all all of those
problems like better handling of name
spaces
less memory consumption less document
centricity
etc etc a bunch of different things that
people have complained about over the
years
um well that's great and so this this
creates a whole new exciting uh
programming experience for xml so let me
just try and first new up an element and
then
just do console.writeline of that xml
element and see what happens when we run
we just get an empty
xml element called result so here's one
little change from the dom is the
tostring method of an xml element gives
you the xml
nice which seems a fairly logical thing
to do but but
you know we haven't done that before um
now one of the one of the interesting
things about
uh x-link is that an xml element has a
constructor
that allows you to specify the contents
of the element right there as you're
newing it up
so instead of having this very
imperative style of construction that we
have today where you first create an
element and then add
child at child and then append that to
something else
well here you just get to knew it up and
then in the constructor call say what
you want to put in it
okay so one thing i might want to put in
it is the string hello
for example and now i'm just creating an
element called result with
the content hello and if i do that
you'll see i get a little
result with the console hello um i could
try and put in
an attribute called hello
with the value five for example let's
try and run that
oops up i should say new x attribute
let's try and run that and now i get
result with an attribute
called hello with the value five i could
also put in a nested element
called hello containing the value five
and if i run that
i get result containing hello with the
value five very nice as you sort of see
it's fairly
intuitive how you put together the xml
here and you can shape it but the real
kicker is
if what i give as an argument here is
not a string nor an element or an
attribute
but it's something that can be
enumerated
like a query then the constructor will
enumerate the query
and make that the contents fantastic so
now i could say
from c in customers
select new x element
off contact comma c dot company
and let's try and run this guy down and
boom
now i turned my little customer array
into
an xml document containing all other
company names fantastic
and of course i could control the shape
of the xml in here
i might for example say well what i
really want is
an attribute called name
containing the company name whoops and
and another attribute
called phone let's get rid of that
containing c dot phone
there let's try and run this guy and now
you see the shape changes
i'm basically seeing contact name equals
blah phone equals blog name it goes
blackboard
and finally i could of course add a
filter here
and say where c dot city
equals london
and try and run this and now i'm
actually sort of back to the same query
i was writing before right
but this time it comes out as an xml
document so you see
again the power of it here is that i can
take data from one domain
query it and produce data in another
domain completely seamlessly which is
something that we've never been able to
do
um so that's sort of a real brief
overview of the stuff that we're
delivering there's a lot of depth here
where we're
we're giving out a bunch of
documentation samples that come with
this so
you know i encourage everybody to like
get a hold of it absolutely and play
with it
yeah now the um in
future incarnations it's going to be
more strongly typed in the ide
yeah before you say from c in customers
then when i say c
dot oh you will see statement completion
yes so so far
you see we have like the colorization in
there and sort of some basic stuff but
yes that's why this is preview bits and
not final products
absolutely so for so for example when i
want to hit say the channel 9 database
because i'm definitely you know when the
time comes i'm going to want to do this
kind of stuff
yes yeah sequel cursors i mean i
i'm always going to have to do that in
sql but i would imagine right
um so i don't know why i said that but
no way
you can do it do that okay yeah
fantastic you run our tool you point it
at your database that gives you an
object view of your of your channel line
database and then off you are coding in
c sharp beautiful
yeah or maybe ultimately this will be
this is not a c-sharp thing this is a
net thing so this is a capability that
we're building for c-sharp as well as
for vb
cool i mean there's still i mean the
point is there's still going to be
a lot of work that you do in the
database right i mean you're going to
have
to go in you're going to have to write
compound stored procedures and cursors
this is a great way to have um
say on a team you can have the dv
guy create these classes and import
stuff and everything and then now you
have a c-sharp guy can come in actually
it'll make sense to him oh yeah i need
to
run a query about i don't have to ask
this person about what's in the
customer's table
right i can do these queries sure simple
query i think
you know there's not one single answer
that fits everybody in the database
space some people
believe in doing all the logic in the
database and only calling sprock's
even for queries which which of course
limits the query ability the
the dynamicness of the queries obviously
absolutely
other organization i see exactly the
reverse you know they believe in putting
all of the logic in the middle tier
this becomes very useful for that or
what i probably see most typically
is that you limit all modifications of
the database to sprock's
but you do your querying using dynamic
sql
and that's actually a model that we
support very well
because you can you can i i talked about
how we can do dynamic
change tracking on these entities that
you fetch from the database but then
when it comes time to push the changes
back to the database
we can either generate insert update or
delete statements or we can call sprocks
that do
all of the modifications of the database
fantastic
so this is great stuff yeah i should
point out like
one of the other things and anderson get
to share this example is you can use it
on
any data type so you really like sql
it has great programming uh capability
you can
go and reflect your registry and say
select all
where keys have been updated in the last
couple days and find spyware on your
machine
someone would have to build an object
encapsulation of the registry first
but sure it is entirely possible for
today
and with reflection anything any
absolutely any collection so if you have
you know you're creating a windows app
and there's 20 buttons on your screen
that you want to disable
you can say you know find all buttons
where the type is button
and set enabled equals to false so it's
it really is the power of sql
programming
across any of the different data types
whether it's objects
uh data or xml it's it if anybody that's
programming sql will absolutely love it
so now
could you do reflect this against other
uh objects in c sharp other assemblies
like i mean
oh yeah it's another one one of the
little demos i do is like a query to
determine what are the methods of
the string type and then you know i
don't know if you want me to show you
okay okay okay let's let's let's do that
one yeah
let's got this out here and then let's
put in uh our object number
right of cue again here okay so let's
like write a query here
and we want to find out what are the
methods of the string type
so we'll say from m in
type of string dot get
methods which is
returns an array of method infos right
that we're calling m
and then from each m we're going to
select m.name
and let's just start with that as our
query let's try and run it
and then boom here we see all of the
methods defined in
type string sure of course the first
thing we notice is that they're not
sorted alphabetically
so so let's sort them order by
m.name see that now they all come out
alphabetically now we might notice oh
we're just interested in instance
methods
on string okay so we don't want compare
and concat
and whatever the other static methods
are so we can add a where clause
where not m is static
because is static is a property on a
method info and we don't we want all the
non-static ones
and now you see that those guys went
away up here
and then maybe the next thing we notice
is uh gosh there are
six index offs because of overload
so maybe what we want to do is we want
to say
group m by m.name so
group them up by name okay
and we can stop there and just see what
the shape of what comes out
is
and what we see here now is we get a
sequence of something that has a key
field and a group
field the key is the thing we group by
the group fielder all the all of the
elements in that group
and now we could try and shape this a
little bit better
so we could say take that and put it
into
something called g
and then select from that
and we'll project out uh some a field
called method which equals g dot key
and then a field called overload which
is the number of overloads and that we
will set equal to
g.group.com
like so so let's try and run that
and now we see a nice little dump of
the methods of strings sorted
alphabetically grouped up by
how many overloads there are um you know
printed out so
yeah you can in five lines of code you
can
you can query anything with this stuff
that's very cool yeah now uh
yeah i was going to say if you want to
do that just using reflection it's a
little more
laborious but you know they're all this
is using reflection well i mean
i mean by directly yes that's what i
meant yeah you have to write a bunch of
this
for each loop and then you'd have to put
them in a dictionary in order to group
them
yeah yeah yeah yeah so i mean
there is something to be said for the
the the sql syntax transact sql
is really pretty nifty in many ways yeah
but this isn't this
is this is like sql it is not sql syntax
but it's the same idea
it's a more declarative way of stating
what you want done
and that's really i think the big
difference between this type of
programming and
and the traditional way where where
today when we write our programs
a lot of the time we are not just saying
what we want done but we are in
meticulous detail specifying how we want
it done
do you know what i mean like take create
this xml element add it as a child of
that
and we're like writing all of these
assembly like instructions
you know instead of stating at a higher
level like this
how what we want done and then having
the system figure out how to do it
fantastic yes great
how do we get this uh so it it'll be
available uh we'll have the tech preview
bits available on msdn
and it'll be msdn.microsoft.com slash
net framework slash futures and that
includes everything you just need
beta2 and you can start uh writing your
queries right with all that stuff all
the overview docs and we'll have uh
hundreds of
100 queries on the web is this another
free update
do we have to pay money for this uh no
this is totally free it's just uh
is still going to make any money a small
msi again it's a tech preview so
uh keep those things in mind okay and
feedback is incredibly important
right we have uh in fact on the on the
msdn
link that dan mentioned there will be uh
there'll be a link to
uh forums and whatever where we'd love
to hear feedback
sure very cool yeah i think
it was great from our first conversation
i think it was about a year ago when we
were in the
uh what was it the museum yeah we barely
touched and got
yeah we were in the middle of cooking
this thing while we told you so when we
come back next what are you going to
have shots
[Laughter]
anders is picking up some more stuff
well this is great yeah thank you
all right take care all right absolutely
Subtitles End: mo.dbxdb.com